<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>The Emperiall acheiuement of our dread soueraigne King Charles together wth ye armes crests supporters &amp; mottowes of all ye seuerall companies &amp; corporations of ye famous citty of London as they now beare them</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1635</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 6 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 8 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2011-12">2011-12 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A18462</idno>
            <idno type="STC">STC 5022</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC S117546</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">99852759</idno>
            <idno type="PROQUEST">99852759</idno>
            <idno type="VID">18102</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A18462)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 18102)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1475-1640 ; 1229:26)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>The Emperiall acheiuement of our dread soueraigne King Charles together wth ye armes crests supporters &amp; mottowes of all ye seuerall companies &amp; corporations of ye famous citty of London as they now beare them</title>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>Are to be sould by William Webb at his shopp at ye signe of ye Globe in Cornehill ouer aganist ye Royall Exchange,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
                  <date>[ca. 1635]</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Publication date conjectured by STC.</note>
                  <note>Consists of engraved title page and at least 60 numbered and 5 unnumbered coats of arms.--STC.</note>
                  <note>STC unsure of format.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Charles --  I, --  King of England, 1600-1649.</term>
               <term>Guilds --  England --  London --  Early works to 1800.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2010-01</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-01</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-04</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-04</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2011-06</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="engraved_title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:18102:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:18102:1"/>
            <p>
               <figure>
                  <q>HONI SOIT QVI MAL Y PENSE</q>
                  <q>DIEV ET MON DROIT</q>
                  <figDesc>blazon of the House of Stuart</figDesc>
                  <p>The Emperiall acheiuement of ourdread Soueraigne King Charl<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>s together w<hi rend="sup">t</hi>h y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> Armes Crests Supporters &amp; mottowes of all y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> ſeuerall Companies &amp; Corporations of y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> famous Citty of London as they now heare them Are to be sould by William Webb at his shopp at y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> ſigne of y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> Globe in Cornehill ouer against y<hi rend="sup">e</hi> Royall Exchange</p>
               </figure>
            </p>
            <list>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Marcha: of Staple:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Merchants of the Staple</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Marcha: of Cloth:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Cloth Merchants</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Muscovie: Marcha</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Merchants of Muscovy</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Marcha: of Fran:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Merchants of France</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Mar: of Spain:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Merchants of Spain</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Est Land Compa:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the English Eastland Company</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Westindia: Comp:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Dutch West India Company</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Dutch: Compa:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Dutch East India Company</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>Virginia: Compa:</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Virginia Company</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
            </list>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="list_of_coats_of_arms">
            <pb facs="tcp:18102:2"/>
            <list>
               <pb facs="tcp:18102:2" rendition="simple:additions"/>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful City of London</figDesc>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>The Turkie Companey</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Turkey (Levant) Company</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>The East India Companie</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the East India Company</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">DEVS INDEAT</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>The Marchant Adventurers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Company of Merchant Adventurers</figDesc>
                     <q>GOD BI OVR DEFENCE:</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:3" rendition="simple:additions"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>1 The Mercers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Mercers</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">HONOR DEO</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>2 The Grocers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Grocers</figDesc>
                     <q>GOD GRANT GRACE</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>3 the Drapers.</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Drapers</figDesc>
                     <q>VNTO GOD ONLY BE HONR GLORY</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>4 the Fiſhmongers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Fishmongers</figDesc>
                     <q>AL WOR. BE TO GOD ONLY</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>5 The Goldſmiths</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Goldsmiths</figDesc>
                     <q>TO GOD ONLY BE ALL GLORY</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>6 The Skinners</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Skinners</figDesc>
                     <q>TO GOD ONLY BE AL GLORY</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:3" rendition="simple:additions"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>7 The Merchantaylors</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Merchant Taylors</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">Concordia parua<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap> Res. creſcunt</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>8 The Haberdaſhers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Haberdashers</figDesc>
                     <q>SERVE AND OR<gap reason="illegible" extent="1 letter">
                           <desc>•</desc>
                        </gap>AR</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>9 The Salters</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Salters</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">SAL SAPIT OMNIA</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>10 The Iromongers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Ironmongers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>11 The Vintner</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Vintners</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>12 The Clothworkers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Clothworkers</figDesc>
                     <q>MY TRVST IS IN GOD ALONE</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:4"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>13 The Diers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Dyers</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">DA GLORIAM DEO</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>14 the Bruers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Brewers</figDesc>
                     <q>IN GOD IS ALL OVR TRVST</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>15 The letherſellers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Leathersellers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>16 The Peuterers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Pewterers</figDesc>
                     <q>IN GOD IS ALL MY TRVST</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>17 The Barberſurgeons</head>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">DE PRICIPIENCIA DEI</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>18 The Armorers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Armorers</figDesc>
                     <q>MAKE ALL SHVER</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:4" rendition="simple:additions"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>19 The White bakers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of White Bakers</figDesc>
                     <q>PRAIS GOD FOR ALL</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>20 The Waxchandler</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Wax Chandlers</figDesc>
                     <q>TRV THIS THE LIGHT</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>s. 21 The Tallowchundlers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Tallow Chandlers</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">Ecce agnus Dei qui tollit pecatia mundi</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>22 The Cutlers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Cutlers</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="frm">POVR PORVENIR A BONNE FOY</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>23 The Girdlers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Girdlers</figDesc>
                     <q>GIVE THANKS TO GOD</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>24 The Butchers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Butchers</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">
                        <abbr>Oia</abbr> subieciſti ſub pedibus oues et boues</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:5"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>25 The Sadlers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Saddlers</figDesc>
                     <q>OVR TRVST IS IN GOD.</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>26 The Carpenters</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Carpenters</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>27 the Shoomakers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Shoemakers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>28 the Painters</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Painter-Stainers</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">AMOR QVEAT OBEDIENCIA</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>29 the Curriers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Curriers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>30 the Maſons</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Masons</figDesc>
                     <q>IN THE LORD IS AL OVR <hi>Trust</hi>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:5" rendition="simple:additions"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>31 the Plimmers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Plumbers</figDesc>
                     <q>IN GOD IS OVR HOPE</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>32 the Inholders</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Innholders</figDesc>
                     <q>Com ye bleſſed when i was harberles ye loged me</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>33 the Founders</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Founders</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>34 the Embrotherer</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Broderers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>35 the Poutters</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Poulters</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>36 the Cookes</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Cooks</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:6"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>37 the Coopers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Coopers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>38 the Briklayers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Tilers and Bricklayers</figDesc>
                     <q>IN GOD IS AL OVR <hi>Trust</hi>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>39 the Bowyers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Bowyers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>40 the Fletchers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Fletchers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>41 the Smithes</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Blacksmiths</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>42 the Ioyneres</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Joiners and Ceilers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:6" rendition="simple:additions"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>43 the Plaſterers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Plaisterers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>44 the Weaueres</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Weavers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>45 the Fruiterers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Fruiterers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>46 the Scriuener</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Scriveners</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>47 Botle makers-horners</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Horners</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>48 the Stationers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Stationers</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">PER BENE NATIS MALE VIVRE</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:7"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>49 the Marblers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Marblers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>50 the Woolpackers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Woolmen</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>51 the Farriers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Farriers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>52 the Pauiors</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Paviors</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>53 the Lorinors</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Loriners</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>54 the Browne Bakers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Brown Bakers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:7" rendition="simple:additions"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>55 the Woodmongrs</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Woodmongers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>56 the <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>pholſters</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Upholders</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>57 the Turners</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Turners</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>58 the Glaſiers<g ref="char:punc">▪</g>
                     </head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Glaziers</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>59 the Clarkes<g ref="char:punc">▪</g>
                     </head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Clerks</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <figure>
                     <head>60 the Watermen</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Watermen</figDesc>
                     <q>
                        <gap reason="blank" extent="1 span">
                           <desc>〈1 span left blank〉</desc>
                        </gap>
                     </q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <pb facs="tcp:18102:8"/>
                  <figure>
                     <head>61 The Apothicariers</head>
                     <figDesc>blazon of the Worshipful Company of Apothecaries</figDesc>
                     <q xml:lang="lat">OPIFERQVE: PER: ORBEM: DICOR:</q>
                  </figure>
               </item>
            </list>
            <pb facs="tcp:18102:8" rendition="simple:additions"/>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
